♪The ringtone of the youth♪
♪ نغمة الشباب
♪The smell of your hair in the convenience store♪
♪ رائحة شعرك في المتجر ♪
♪The best and cutest smile♪
♪ احلى و احلى ابتسامة ♪
♪It's exactly what I'm looking for♪
♪ هذا بالضبط ما أبحث عنه
♪Run, run, run♪
♪ تشغيل ، تشغيل ، تشغيل ♪
♪My love, meow, meow, meow♪
♪ حبي ، مواء ، مواء ، مواء ♪
♪I miss you, you, you♪
♪ اشتقت لك ، أنت ، أنت ♪
♪The arrow ready to be shot♪
♪ السهم جاهز للتصوير
♪Ready at all time♪
♪ جاهز في كل وقت ♪
♪My love for you is like the shot arrow♪
♪ حبي لك مثل سهم النار ♪
♪Never step down♪
♪ لا تتنازل أبدًا
♪All the irritating rumour♪
كل الشائعات المزعجة
♪Will be pushed back by me♪
♪ سأدفعه للخلف بواسطتي
♪Every moment we hug♪
♪ كل لحظة نعانقها ♪
♪It hits the target of sweetness♪
تضرب هدف الحلاوة ♪
♪It's simple to have everything of you♪
♪ من السهل أن يكون لديك كل شيء
♪My love for you is like the shot arrow♪
♪ حبي لك مثل سهم النار ♪
♪Never step down♪
♪ لا تتنازل أبدًا
♪All the irritating rumour♪
كل الشائعات المزعجة
♪Will be pushed back by me♪
♪ سأدفعه للخلف بواسطتي
♪The wind blown by the summer♪
الرياح تهب بفعل الصيف ♪
♪It passes by the stars in the sky♪
يمر بالنجوم في السماء
♪This crazy arrow♪
♪ هذا السهم المجنون ♪
♪Shoots at the target of love♪
♪ يطلق النار على هدف الحب ♪
=Aim the Heart! Archeress=
= هدف القلب!  آرتشر =
=Episode 8=
= الحلقة 8 =
(Kitchen)
(مطبخ)
Your noodles are ready.
المعكرونة جاهزة.
All right.
حسنا.
Enjoy.
يتمتع.
Boss, I'm done.
بوس ، لقد انتهيت.
- All right. - Goodbye.
- حسنا.  - مع السلامة.
See you.
أرك لاحقًا.
(Breaking News. The has-been is dating a girl in a sports school.)
(الأخبار العاجلة. لقد كان يواعد فتاة في مدرسة رياضية.)
(Han Jiangshuo meets up with a girl of sports school. Lovey-dovey.)
(يلتقي هان جيانجشو بفتاة في مدرسة رياضية. لوفي دوفي.)
What a brat!
يا له من شقي!
Let's see what I'll do to you!
دعنا نرى ما سأفعله لك!
Cai.
تساي.
Why are you so mad?
لماذا أنت هكذا جنون؟
You're just discharged.
لقد خرجت للتو.
You've just recovered.
لقد تعافيت للتو.
Look at this.
انظر إلى هذا.
What kind of a person is this?
أي نوع من الأشخاص هذا؟
Yezi is naive.
Yezi ساذج.
She must have been tricked.
لابد أنها تعرضت للخداع.
Cai, calm down.
تساي ، اهدأ.
Take a seat. Let me take a look.
اجلس.  دعني ألقي نظرة.
(Han Jiangshuo meets up with a girl of sports school. Lovey-dovey.)
(يلتقي هان جيانجشو بفتاة في مدرسة رياضية. لوفي دوفي.)
I've seen this guy before.
لقد رأيت هذا الرجل من قبل.
He helped out here. He was quite hardworking.
لقد ساعد هنا.  كان مجتهدًا جدًا.
He didn't seem like a bad person.
لا يبدو أنه شخص سيء.
What?
ماذا؟
He's been here?
هل كان هنا؟
Why didn't I know this?
لماذا لم اعرف هذا؟
Why didn't you tell me?
لماذا لم تخبرني
This won't do. I must speak to him.
هذا لن ينفع.  يجب أن أتحدث معه.
Let the young people
دع الشباب
handle their matters themselves.
يتعاملون مع أمورهم بأنفسهم.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I still feel troubled.
ما زلت أشعر بالضيق.
She's all grown up now.
لقد كبرت الآن.
Even if you look for her now,
حتى لو كنت تبحث عنها الآن ،
it won't look nice.
لن تبدو جميلة.
Yezi will be back in a short time.
Yezi سوف يعود في وقت قصير.
We can talk to her then.
يمكننا التحدث معها بعد ذلك.
(They feed each other food.)
(إنهم يطعمون بعضهم البعض طعامًا.)
I think they are well-matched.
أعتقد أنهم متقاربون.
I've run ten laps already.
لقد ركضت عشر لفات بالفعل.
I cannot run anymore.
لا أستطيع الركض بعد الآن.
We can complete everything with another round.
يمكننا إكمال كل شيء بجولة أخرى.
Ziwen! You can do this!
زيوين!  يمكنك القيام بالأمر!
No more.
لا أكثر.
Who wants to lose weight in a 100 days?
من يريد إنقاص وزنه في 100 يوم؟
It's so tiring.
إنه متعب للغاية.
Why don't you
لماذا لا
give me a bite of chocolate?
أعطني قطعة من الشوكولاتة؟
Then, I'll continue.
ثم سأستمر.
How about this?
وماذا عن هذا؟
If you can outrun me,
إذا كنت تستطيع الهروب مني ،
I'll give you a bite.
سأعطيك عضة.
How can you do that?
كيف يمكنك فعل ذلك؟
Forget it then.
ننسى ذلك الحين.
I...
أنا...
You can do this!
يمكنك القيام بالأمر!
Keep up!
ابق كما أنت!
Success is in front of you!
النجاح أمامك!
You can do this!
يمكنك القيام بالأمر!
Outrun me!
تجاوزني!
Outrun me and you'll get a bite of chocolate!
تجاوزني وستحصل على قطعة من الشوكولاتة!
Think of the sweet fragrance
فكر في العطر الحلو
and the sweet taste.
والطعم الحلو.
You can do this!
يمكنك القيام بالأمر!
Ziwen!
زيوين!
Lin Ziwen, you can do this!
لين زيوين ، يمكنك القيام بذلك!
(Forget it.)
(انسى ذلك.)
(I'll let you have a bite today.)
(سأتركك تتناول قضمة اليوم.)
Li Jiahao, I've outrun you!
لي جياهاو ، لقد تفوقت عليك!
I outran you!
أنا أتفوق عليك!
If my laces didn't come undone,
إذا لم تتراجع الأربطة ،
how could you outrun me?
كيف يمكنك الهروب مني؟
I don't care.
لا أهتم.
Keep your promise.
حافظ على وعدك.
Just a small bite.
مجرد لدغة صغيرة.
One small bite.
لدغة واحدة صغيرة.
Got it.
فهمتك.
This chocolate tastes weird.
طعم هذه الشوكولاتة غريب.
Is it fake?
هل هي مزيفة؟
I knew this would happen.
أنا أعلم أن هذا سيحدث.
So, I bought dried tofu.
لذا اشتريت التوفو المجفف.
Not only will not gain weight
ليس فقط لن يكتسب الوزن
but also can supplement nutrition.
ولكن يمكن أيضا أن تكون مكملة للتغذية.
Li Jiahao.
لي جياهاو.
Just you wait!
فقط انتظر!
Li Jiahao! You...
لي جياهاو! أنت ...
You...
أنت...
Ziwen!
زيوين!
Ziwen, it's not my fault.
Ziwen ، هذا ليس خطأي.
Who are you?
من أنت؟
Li Jiahao.
لي جياهاو.
It's me.
هذا أنا.
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
Are you on a secret mission?
هل أنت في مهمة سرية؟
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
I'm here to recruit you on behalf of the organization.
أنا هنا لتجنيدك نيابة عن المنظمة.
We might be spotted here. Come with me.
قد يتم رصدنا هنا.  تعال معي.
Let's find a safe spot.
دعنا نجد مكانا آمنا.
All right. A secret place.
حسنا.  مكان سري.
(Teaching Building 2)
(مبنى التدريس 2)
Ruofei
Ruofei
What's the matter?
ما الأمر؟
I want to show you something.
اريد ان اريك شيئا.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
Let me see.
دعني أرى.
Copycat Magazine?
مجلة التقليد؟
This is a lame tabloid.
هذه صحيفة تابلويد واهية.
(Han Jiangshuo meets up with a girl) What an amateur camera angle.
(يلتقي هان جيانغشو بفتاة) يا لها من زاوية كاميرا للهواة.
He didn't even capture Cai Jinye's face properly.
حتى أنه لم يلتقط وجه كاي جيني بشكل صحيح.
The writing is mediocre as well.
الكتابة متواضعة كذلك.
Please.
لو سمحت.
I didn't ask you to come here to criticise the piece.
لم أطلب منك المجيء إلى هنا لانتقاد القطعة.
However,
لكن،
how can you tell this is Cai Jinye?
كيف يمكنك معرفة أن هذا هو تساي جينيني؟
Who am I?
من أنا؟
I am the prince
انا الامير
of Jianghang University of Sports,
من جامعة Jianghang للرياضة ،
adored by both fans and sponsors.
يعشقه كل من المعجبين والجهات الراعية.
I managed to achieve that
تمكنت من تحقيق ذلك
with my sharp insights,
بآرائي الحادة ،
sophisticated analysis
تحليل متطور
and my agile mind.
وعقلي رشيق.
Ruofei
Ruofei
do you think I'll stand a chance as a paparazzi?
هل تعتقد أنني سأحظى بفرصة بصفتي مصورون مصورون؟
I'll look for someone else.
سأبحث عن شخص آخر.
Ruofei, please listen to me.
Ruofei ، يرجى الاستماع إلي.
It's all because
كل هذا بسبب
of that affectionate gaze of yours.
من تلك النظرة الحنونة لك.
Of course Cai Jinye was the girl sitting right across you.
بالطبع كانت كاي جيني الفتاة التي تجلس أمامك.
Affectionate gaze? What do you mean?
نظرة حنون؟  ماذا تقصد بذلك؟
It's all about the angle, got it?
الأمر كله يتعلق بالزاوية ، فهمت؟
In the entertainment industry, as long as two lock eyes,
في صناعة الترفيه ، طالما أن قفل العينين ،
the paparazzi would create
المصورون سيخلقون
a tragic romance out of it.
قصة حب مأساوية للخروج منه.
Ruofei, don't panic.
Ruofei ، لا داعي للذعر.
I suspect that Curvy Corgi
أظن أن Curvy Corgi
isn't a professional paparazzo.
ليس مصورًا محترفًا.
Why?
لماذا ا؟
Look.
نظرة.
You've been out of the spotlight for so long.
لقد كنت خارج دائرة الضوء لفترة طويلة.
Why would a professional paparazzo focus on you?
لماذا قد يركز المصورون المحترفون عليك؟
No. I mean that you've been
لا ، أعني أنك كنت كذلك
keeping a low profile these days.
الحفاظ على الانظار هذه الأيام.
You don't get exposed much.
لا تتعرض كثيرًا.
Why would the busy paparazzi
لماذا المصورون مشغولون
focus on you? Am I right?
التركيز عليك؟  هل انا على حق؟
That makes sense.
منطقي.
Also,
ايضا،
according to my analysis,
وفقًا لتحليلي ،
Curvy Corgi is familiar with your schedule.
Curvy Corgi على دراية بجدولك الزمني.
This is a bad camera angle.
هذه زاوية كاميرا سيئة.
The composition and the colour tones are off.
التكوين ودرجات اللون متوقفة.
The resolution is very low.
الدقة منخفضة للغاية.
No matter how I look at it,
مهما نظرت إليه ،
the skills are an amateur's.
المهارات هي للهواة.
Go on.
تابع.
According to my analysis,
وفقًا لتحليلي ،
I am sure the writer, Curvy Corgi,
أنا متأكد من أن الكاتب ، كورفي كورجي ،
is our schoolmate.
هو زميلنا في المدرسة.
You're finally being useful.
لقد أصبحت أخيرًا مفيدًا.
I'm very glad.
انا مسرور جدا.
Really?
هل حقا؟
Hold my bag.
امسك حقيبتي.
You are finally appreciating my talent.
أنت أخيرا تقدر موهبتي.
(Breaking News. The has-been is dating a girl in a sports school.)
(الأخبار العاجلة. لقد كان يواعد فتاة في مدرسة رياضية.)
Captain, are you reading a magazine?
كابتن ، هل تقرأ مجلة؟
When did you two get together?
متى اجتمعتما معا؟
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد بذلك؟
Why don't I understand you?
لماذا لا افهمك
Stop pretending.
كف عن التظاهر.
Do you think we didn't see this?
هل تعتقد أننا لم نر هذا؟
How could you hide your relationship from your best friends?
كيف يمكنك إخفاء علاقتك عن أعز أصدقائك؟
Lower your voice.
اخفض صوتك.
What are you talking about?
ما الذي تتحدث عنه؟
It's in Copycat Magazine.
إنه في مجلة Copycat.
The whole school knows by now.
المدرسة كلها تعرف الآن.
Yezi, you're blushing.
Yezi ، أنت تحمر خجلاً.
Enough of your nonsense.
كفى من هذا الهراء.
Are you still not admitting it?
هل ما زلت لا تعترف بذلك؟
I feel that our friendship
أشعر أن صداقتنا
is facing a unprecedented setback.
يواجه انتكاسة غير مسبوقة.
I'm seriously not dating him.
أنا بجدية لا أواعده.
It's just fake news.
إنها مجرد أخبار مزيفة.
Is the part on the hotel fake, too?
هل الجزء الموجود في الفندق مزيف أيضًا؟
That's true.
هذا صحيح.
Then, the fact that he touched your face
ثم حقيقة أنه لمس وجهك
must be true, too, right?
يجب أن يكون صحيحًا أيضًا ، أليس كذلك؟
It's fake.
انه مزيف.
Give that back to me.
أعد ذلك إلي.
Gather around!
يجتمع حول!
Let's take a look.
لنلقي نظرة.
- What's there to see? - It's time to gather.
- ماذا هناك لنرى؟  - حان وقت التجمع.
Let me take a look.
دعني ألقي نظرة.
Don't snatch it.
لا تنتزعها.
What are you all doing?
ماذا تفعلون؟
- Coach.
- مدرب رياضي.  - مدرب رياضي.
Hurry up.
عجلوا.
I'll say one thing.
سأقول شيئًا واحدًا.
Recently, some students
في الآونة الأخيرة ، بعض الطلاب
are not focusing on their training.
لا يركزون على تدريبهم.
They're busy thinking
إنهم مشغولون بالتفكير
of other things.
من أشياء أخرى.
Starting today,
ابتداء من اليوم ،
everyone here must
يجب على الجميع هنا
focus all attention
تركز كل الاهتمام
on unlimited training.
على تدريب غير محدود.
I announced that starting today,
لقد أعلنت أنه بدءًا من اليوم ،
the guys and girls will train separately.
سيتدرب الرجال والفتيات بشكل منفصل.
Train separately?
تدريب منفصل؟
Why?
لماذا ا؟
Please ensure appropriate
يرجى التأكد من الملاءمة
contact between students.
الاتصال بين الطلاب.
Got it?
فهمتك؟
Yes, coach.
نعم مدرب.
Cai Jinye, especially,
Cai Jinye ، على وجه الخصوص ،
cannot leave
لا يمكن ترك
school premises without my permission.
مباني المدرسة بدون إذني.
Dismiss.
رفض.
Cai Jinye.
كاي جيني.
Coach.
مدرب رياضي.
Come with me to my office.
تعال معي إلى مكتبي.
Ziwen and Yuling.
Ziwen و Yuling.
I feel like my world
أشعر وكأنني عالمي
is about to crumble.
على وشك الانهيار.
You can do this.
يمكنك القيام بالأمر.
Take care.
يعتني.
No.
رقم.
Don't leave me.
لا تتركنى.
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Have some water.
اشرب بعض الماء.
Thank you, coach.
شكرا لك مدرب.
Yezi.
هذه هي.
In certain matters,
في بعض الأمور ،
I'm sure you know better without me saying it.
أنا متأكد من أنك تعرف أفضل دون أن أقول ذلك.
Currently, the most important thing is
حاليا ، أهم شيء هو
for you to focus all your effort
لكي تركز كل ما تبذلونه من جهد
on the training and the competition.
على التدريب والمنافسة.
Don't be affected
لا تتأثر
by complicated matters like relationships.
من خلال الأمور المعقدة مثل العلاقات.
Otherwise, you will have waste all your effort.
خلاف ذلك ، سوف تضيع كل ما تبذلونه من جهد.
Yezi, do you understand?
ييزي ، هل تفهم؟
there are someting
هناك وقت
you may handle it in the future.
يمكنك التعامل معها في المستقبل.
Certain feelings
مشاعر معينة
can only be protected properly
لا يمكن إلا أن تكون محمية بشكل صحيح
when you're more mature.
عندما تكون أكثر نضجًا.
Back then,
في ذلك الوقت،
I was young and frivolous, too.
كنت صغيرا وتافها أيضا.
And I was innocent and naive.
وكنت بريئا وساذجا.
I lost everything in the end.
لقد فقدت كل شيء في النهاية.
Yezi, do you understand?
ييزي ، هل تفهم؟
That year,
تلك السنة،
as the flower petals fell, apricot blossom rain.
كما سقطت بتلات الزهور ، مطر زهر المشمش.
We've known each other since we were nine or ten.
لقد عرفنا بعضنا البعض منذ أن كنا في التاسعة أو العاشرة.
We talked about the future, too.
تحدثنا عن المستقبل أيضًا.
We were very much in love.
كنا كثيرا في الحب.
However,
لكن،
it was all unreal.
كان كل شيء غير واقعي.
She pretended to be my girlfriend
لقد تظاهرت بأنها صديقتي
to distract me from training
لإلهائي عن التدريب
and cause me to lose my position.
وتجعلني أفقد منصبي.
Lv,
Lv
you're so cruel.
انت قاسي جدا.
Coach,
مدرب رياضي،
who is Lv?
من هو Lv؟
Lv.
Lv.
That's none of your business.
ليس من شأنك.
What are you still doing here?
ما الذي لازلت تفعله هنا؟
Go for training.
اذهب للتدريب.
I...
أنا...
(Weren't you lecturing me?)
(ألم تحاضرني؟)
All right, coach.
حسنًا أيها المدرب.
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
I'm so annoyed.
أنا منزعج جدا.
(Non-training hours. Only open to students.)
(غير ساعات التدريب. مفتوح للطلاب فقط).
I'm exhausted.
أنا مرهق.
We've been doing it for a day. Let's go.
كنا نفعل ذلك ليوم واحد.  لنذهب.
You swam well earlier on.
لقد سبحت جيدًا في وقت سابق.
Do you have water?
هل لديك ماء؟
No.
رقم.
I'm so thirsty.
أنا عطشان جدآ.
- Let's buy some. - You'll go.
- لنشتري بعضا منها.  - انت سوف تذهب.
You should go.
يجب أن تذهب.
Me?
أنا؟
I'm not going.
أنا لن أذهب.
What a nice figure.
يا له من شخصية جميلة.
Yanjun.
يانجون.
What are you looking at?
الى ماذا تنظرين؟
Have you never seen a beautiful girl before?
ألم ترَ فتاة جميلة من قبل؟
Help!
مساعدة!
Senior!
كبير!
Help! Senior!
مساعدة!  كبير!
(She was swimming well earlier on.)
(كانت تسبح جيدًا في وقت سابق).
(Why can't she swim suddenly?)
(لماذا لا تستطيع السباحة فجأة؟)
Give me your hand.
اعطني يدك.
(How dare you try to pretend in front of me.)
(كيف تجرؤ على التظاهر أمامي).
Go forward.
تقدم للامام.
Jiang Yanjun, help me.
جيانغ يانجون ، ساعدني.
I have a leg cramp.
أعاني من تشنج في الساق.
Someone is drowning.
شخص ما يغرق.
Yanjun.
يانجون.
Get on first.
ابدأ أولاً.
Help!
مساعدة!
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
- Let me go. - We're coming.
- دعني أذهب.  - نحن قادمون.
Let me go.
دعني اذهب.
Yanjun. Jiang Yanjun.
يانجون جيانغ يانجون.
- Let me go. - Be careful.
- دعني أذهب.  - كن حذرا.
- Here.
- كن حذرا.  - هنا.
Are you all right?
هل انت بخير؟
Let me go.
دعني اذهب.
Go away.
يبتعد.
I don't want you to save me.
لا أريدك أن تنقذني.
We were just being nice.
كنا لطفاء فقط.
Yanjun, thank you.
يانجون ، شكرا لك.
Jiang Yanjun,
جيانغ يانجون ،
please agree to accept
الرجاء الموافقة على القبول
the one-on-one interview.
المقابلة الفردية.
(Reject her.)
(ارفضها).
Fine. No problem.
بخير.  لا مشكلة.
I knew the stupid bloke wouldn't reject anyone.
كنت أعلم أن الرجل الغبي لن يرفض أي شخص.
Let me help her.
اسمحوا لي أن أساعدها.
Aren't you going too far just for an interview?
ألا تذهب بعيدًا جدًا لمجرد إجراء مقابلة؟
That's my assignment.
هذه مهمتي.
Why don't you interview me instead?
لماذا لا تقابلني بدلا من ذلك؟
What do you think?
ماذا تعتقد؟
Mengmeng, are you all right?
مينجمينج ، هل أنت بخير؟
I'm fine. Don't worry.
أنا بخير.  لا تقلق.
I'll take good care of her.
سأعتني بها جيدًا.
All right.
حسنا.
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Why is Han Ruofei not here yet?
لماذا هان Ruofei ليس هنا بعد؟
What is he up to?
ما هو انه حتى؟
(It's an expensive phone yet it's not ringing.)
(إنه هاتف باهظ الثمن ولكنه لا يرن.)
(I tickled head of Narcissist Han.) (I like you.)
(أنا دغدغ رأس النرجسي هان.) (أنا معجب بك.)
(Recall the message.)
(اجب على الرساله.)
Who would fall for you?
من سيقع في حبك؟
You're so cute.
انت لطيف جدا.
Are you looking for me?
هل تبحث عني؟
Are you here to sell chocolate?
هل انت هنا لبيع الشوكولاتة؟
No, thank you.
لا، شكرا.
I don't eat chocolate.
أنا لا آكل الشوكولاتة.
It's not because I don't like it.
ليس لأنني لا أحب ذلك.
I'm watching my weight.
أنا أراقب وزني.
So, I'm trying to stay away
لذا ، أحاول الابتعاد
from high-calorie food
من الأطعمة ذات السعرات الحرارية العالية
like chocolate.
مثل الشوكولا.
Anyway, thank you for the thought.
على أي حال ، شكرا لك على الفكر.
I love it actually.
أنا أحبه في الواقع.
Can I take a picture with you?
هل يمكنني التقاط صورة معك؟
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Are you inviting me to the riverside?
هل تدعوني إلى ضفة النهر؟
No. I'm waiting for someone.
رقم أنا في انتظار شخص ما.
Me? You?
أنا؟  أنت؟
Do you mean I'm waiting for you?
هل تقصد انني في انتظارك؟
You...
أنت...
A little bird?
الطيور الصغيرة؟
Fly?
يطير؟
Are you Han Ruofei?
هل أنت هان روفي؟
Why are you dressed like that?
لماذا تلبس هكذا؟
I... No.
انا لا.
You...
أنت...
Han Ruofei, it's really you.
هان روفي ، أنت حقًا.
Lower your voice.
اخفض صوتك.
I'm sorry for what happened these days.
أنا آسف لما حدث هذه الأيام.
It's all my fault.
هذا كله خطأي.
I've caused you so much trouble.
لقد سببت لك الكثير من المتاعب.
To prevent further trouble,
لمنع المزيد من المتاعب ،
I've asked for
لقد طلبت
two days of medical leave.
يومين إجازة مرضية.
What?
ماذا؟
No.
رقم.
You're taking medical leave because of this?
أنت تأخذ إجازة طبية بسبب هذا؟
I don't feel troubled at all.
لا أشعر بالضيق على الإطلاق.
I've decided.
لقد قررت.
No. What did you decide on?
رقم ماذا قررت؟
You stopped going for training.
لقد توقفت عن الذهاب للتدريب.
You stopped going for cultural lessons, too.
لقد توقفت عن الذهاب إلى الدروس الثقافية أيضًا.
You didn't reply to texts nor pick up calls.
أنت لم ترد على الرسائل النصية ولا تلتقط المكالمات.
Do you know how worried I was?
هل تعلم كم كنت قلقة؟
I thought something happened to you.
اعتقدت أن شيئا ما حدث لك.
Are you worried about me?
هل أنت قلق بشأني؟
I...
أنا...
Were you worried about me?
هل كنت قلقة علي؟
That's not the point.
هذا ليس المقصود.
The point is
المقصود هو
you skipped classes.
لقد تخطيت الفصول الدراسية.
Do you know
هل تعرف
how the cultural classes change every day?
كيف تتغير الطبقات الثقافية كل يوم؟
They won't wait for you.
لن ينتظروا منك.
I know.
أنا أعرف.
I...
أنا...
What's so funny?
ما المضحك في ذلك؟
Be serious.
كن جادا.
Fine. I'll be serious.
بخير.  سأكون جادا.
I'll get that paparazzo.
سأحضر هذا المصور.
I'll restore your reputation.
سأعيد سمعتك.
I won't let anyone
لن أسمح لأحد
bully you.
يتنمر عليك.
Oh, no. I forgot to turn off flash.
أوه لا.  لقد نسيت أن أطفئ الفلاش.
Is that...
هل هذا...
Get her!
احصل عليها!
(Shizu Supermarket)
(سوبر ماركت شيزو)
Stop!
قف!
Don't run!
لا تركض!
Han Ruofei!
هان روفي!
Han Ruofei, are you all right?
هان روفي ، هل أنت بخير؟
Are you all right?
هل انت بخير؟
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
Take the alley.
خذ الزقاق.
I'll take this lane.
سآخذ هذا الممر.
Be careful.
كن حذرا.
All right.
حسنا.
The training was so tiring today.
كان التدريب متعبًا للغاية اليوم.
Let's have something nice.
دعونا نحصل على شيء لطيف.
All right.
حسنا.
What do you want to eat?
ماذا تريد أن تأكل؟
Stop there.
توقف هناك.
Help!
مساعدة!
Someone is molesting me!
شخص ما يتحرش بي!
Senior, something happened.
كبير ، حدث شيء ما.
Stop!
قف!
Help!
مساعدة!
- What are you doing? - Stop!
- ماذا تفعل؟  - قف!
- Let go!
- اتركه!  - قف!
Let go!
اتركه!
Stop hitting me! It's me!
توقف عن ضربي!  هذا أنا!
I'm hitting you!
أنا أضربك!
You're quite strong.
أنت قوي جدا.
You won't be able to take it anymore, Jiahao.
لن تكون قادرًا على تناوله بعد الآن ، جياو.
Leave it to me!
اتركه لي!
Stop! He's Han Ruofei.
توقف! إنه هان روفي.
What?
ماذا؟
- Han Ruofei? - How can that be?
- هان روفي؟  - كيف يمكن أن يكون؟
He is really Han Ruofei.
إنه حقًا هان Ruofei.
Han Ruofei.
هان روفي.
Ruofei.
Ruofei.
Where are we?
اين نحن؟
Get up.
استيقظ.
Help him up.
ساعده.
Ruofei.
Ruofei.
Are you all right?
هل انت بخير؟
Ruofei, are you all right?
Ruofei ، هل أنت بخير؟
Han Ruofei, are you all right?
هان روفي ، هل أنت بخير؟
Li Jiahao,
لي جياهاو ،
if not for you,
إن لم يكن لك،
I would've gotten Curvy Corgi.
كنت سأحصل على Curvy Corgi.
Where did she run off?
أين هربت؟
That way, I think.
بهذه الطريقة ، على ما أعتقد.
- Get her! - Stop!
- احصل عليها!  - قف!
Don't move.
.لا تتحرك
I'm Mr. Zhang, a security guard at Jianghang University of Sports.
أنا السيد Zhang ، حارس أمن في جامعة Jianghang للرياضة.
I received a report that
لقد تلقيت تقريرا بذلك
a bear and a girl
دب وفتاة
were causing a commotion.
كانت تسبب جلبة.
It must be you two.
يجب أن تكونا أنتما الاثنان.
Please come to the security office with me.
من فضلك تعال إلى مكتب الأمن معي.
Let's talk at the office.
لنتحدث في المكتب.
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Yezi.
هذه هي.
Ruofei.
Ruofei.
Han Ruofei.
هان روفي.
Sir, it's all a misunderstanding.
سيدي ، كل هذا سوء فهم.
The both of you
كلاكما
are the witnesses.
هم الشهود.
Go back and wait.
ارجع وانتظر.
Go on.
تابع.
Let's go.
لنذهب.
I've caught the suspects.
لقد قبضت على المشتبه بهم.
We're done. Over.
لقد انتهينا.  على.
Han Ruofei. Cai Jinye.
هان روفي. تساي جينيه.
You don't have to say anything if you don't want to.
لست مضطرًا لقول أي شيء إذا كنت لا تريد ذلك.
ou have the right to remain silent.
لديك الحق في التزام الصمت.
Anything you say may be used against you
يمكن استخدام أي شيء تقوله ضدك
in a court of law,
في محكمة قانونية،
understand?
تفهم؟
Sir.
سيد.
Must we be this formal?
هل يجب أن نكون بهذا الشكل الرسمي؟
Do you have any idea
هل لديك أي فكرة
how many reports
كم عدد التقارير
we have received so far?
لقد تلقينا حتى الآن؟
You've messed up the entire back alley of the school.
لقد أفسدت الزقاق الخلفي بأكمله للمدرسة.
You've disrupted the discipline in the school.
لقد عطلتم الانضباط في المدرسة.
Got it.
فهمتك.
Han Ruofei, do you know what you did?
هان روفي ، هل تعرف ماذا فعلت؟
Sir,
سيد،
give us a chance.
اعطنا فرصة.
How should I give you a chance?
كيف اعطيك فرصة؟
I didn't have a choice before this.
لم يكن لدي خيار قبل هذا.
I want to be a good student now.
اريد ان اكون طالبة جيدة الان
Fine. Tell the principal that.
بخير.  أخبر المدير أن.
I'll let him decide.
سأتركه يقرر.
Are you saying I'll be punished?
هل تقول إنني سأعاقب؟
I'm sorry. I'm just a guard.
أنا آسف.  أنا مجرد حارس.
Be serious.
كن جادا.
Dear sir,
سيدى العزيز،
we were framed.
كنا مؤطرين.
Framed?
مؤطر؟
You will eventually pay a price for what you did.
ستدفع في النهاية ثمن ما فعلته.
Nobody can save you.
لا أحد يستطيع أن ينقذك.
Nobody can help you either.
لا احد يستطيع مساعدتك ايضا
You're the one who can save yourself.
أنت من يستطيع إنقاذ نفسك.
I believe the school's rules are fair.
أعتقد أن قواعد المدرسة عادلة.
Sir,
سيد،
I caused the commotion in the back alley.
لقد أحدثت ضجة في الزقاق الخلفي.
Can you let Cai Jinye go first?
هل يمكنك السماح لـ (كاي جيني) بالذهاب أولاً؟
Also,
ايضا،
I hope you won't record her name.
آمل ألا تسجل اسمها.
She is innocent in these things.
إنها بريئة في هذه الأشياء.
Innocent?
بريىء؟
That's not up to you.
هذا ليس متروك لك.
We must investigate it.
يجب علينا التحقيق فيه.
What are you doing this time?
ماذا تفعل هذه المرة؟
You must have been too bored.
لابد أنك كنت تشعر بالملل الشديد.
Hurry up.
عجلوا.
Take down all these messy posters
أزل كل هذه الملصقات الفوضوية
from the wall.
من الحائط.
Han Ruofei and Cai Jinye, right?
Han Ruofei و Cai Jinye ، أليس كذلك؟
We've got to know now
علينا أن نعرف الآن
what has happened.
ماذا حدث.
Ms. Cai can leave first.
يمكن للسيدة كاي المغادرة أولاً.
Mr. Han, please stay back.
السيد هان ، من فضلك ابقى في الخلف.
Will you be all right by alone?
هل ستكون بخير وحدك؟
Yezi,
هؤلاء،
we're buddies.
نحن رفاق.
When you're out, remember to get a good lawyer for me.
عندما تكون بالخارج ، تذكر أن تحصل على محامٍ جيد لي.
Also,
ايضا،
tell Jiahao
اقول Jiahao
to forget me.
أن تنساني.
Are you still messing around?
هل ما زلت تعبث؟
Are you leaving?
هل أنت ذاهب؟
You can stay here with him.
يمكنك البقاء هنا معه.
Fine.
بخير.
All right, I'll wait for you in class.
حسنًا ، سأنتظرك في الفصل.
Don't skip class anymore.
لا تخطي الصف بعد الآن.
Don't worry. I'll be fine.
لا تقلق.  سأكون بخير.
Goodbye.
مع السلامة.
Move aside.
تحرك جانبا.
Are you Han Ruofei?
هل أنت هان روفي؟
♪You always nag♪
انت دائما تذمر ♪
♪When I'm making a decision♪
♪ عندما أتخذ القرار ♪
♪You are always cheerful♪
♪ أنت دائما مبتهج ♪
♪When I'm speechless♪
♪ عندما أكون عاجزًا عن الكلام ♪
♪We lock eyes♪
♪ نغلق العيون
♪And no excess words♪
♪ ولا كلمات زائدة ♪
♪I know you understand me♪
♪ أعلم أنك تفهمني ♪
♪You always have beer♪
♪ لديك دائما بيرة ♪
♪When I'm down♪
♪ عندما أسقط ♪
♪You always support me♪
♪ أنت تدعمني دائمًا ♪
♪When I wanted to give up♪
♪ عندما أردت الاستسلام ♪
♪You accompany me to play a superhero♪
♪ أنت تصاحبني لألعب دور البطل الخارق
♪You become my cape♪
♪ أنت تصبح عرسي ♪
♪So that I can fly high in the sky♪
♪ حتى أتمكن من الطيران عالياً في السماء
♪Behind me♪
♪ ورائي ♪
♪There's a cape♪
♪ هناك عباءة ♪
♪That protects me♪
هذا يحميني ♪
♪No matter what happens♪
♪ مهما حدث
♪You share my dreams♪
♪ أنت تشاركني أحلامي ♪
♪You share my sorrow♪
♪ أنت تشاركني حزني ♪
♪It reminds me♪
إنه يذكرني ♪
♪Not to fall when I'm tired♪
♪ لا أسقط وأنا متعب ♪
♪Behind me♪
♪ ورائي ♪
♪There's a cape♪
♪ هناك عباءة ♪
♪It's like♪
♪ إنها مثل ♪
♪Another me in the world♪
♪ أنا آخر في العالم ♪
♪You know everything about me♪
♪ أنت تعرف كل شيء عني ♪
♪Never back down♪
لا تتراجع أبدًا
♪You're tightly tied to♪
♪ أنت مرتبط بإحكام بـ
♪The left and the right of my shoulders♪
يسار ويمين كتفي ♪
♪The fluttering cape♪
♪ الحرملة المرفرفة ♪
♪Don't forget about me♪
♪ لا تنساني ♪
♪When you're sad♪
♪ عندما تكون حزين ♪
♪I can help you♪
♪ يمكنني مساعدتك ♪
♪Block the wind♪
♪ سد الريح ♪
♪When you're tired♪
♪ عندما تكون متعب ♪
♪I'll be your cape♪
♪ سأكون رداءك ♪
♪So that we can fly high in the sky♪
♪ حتى نتمكن من الطيران عالياً في السماء
♪Behind me♪
♪ ورائي ♪
♪There's a cape♪
♪ هناك عباءة ♪
♪That protects me♪
هذا يحميني ♪
♪No matter what happens♪
♪ مهما حدث
♪You share my dreams♪
♪ أنت تشاركني أحلامي ♪
♪You share my sorrow♪
♪ أنت تشاركني حزني ♪
♪It reminds me♪
إنه يذكرني ♪
♪Not to fall when I'm tired♪
♪ لا أسقط وأنا متعب ♪
♪Behind me♪
♪ ورائي ♪
♪There's a cape♪
♪ هناك عباءة ♪
♪It's like♪
♪ إنها مثل ♪
♪Another me in the world♪
♪ أنا آخر في العالم ♪
♪You know everything about me♪
♪ أنت تعرف كل شيء عني ♪
♪Never back down♪
لا تتراجع أبدًا
♪You're tightly tied to♪
♪ أنت مرتبط بإحكام بـ
♪The left and the right of my shoulders♪
يسار ويمين كتفي ♪
♪Behind me♪
♪ ورائي ♪
♪There's a cape♪
♪ هناك عباءة ♪
♪That protects me♪
هذا يحميني ♪
♪No matter what happens♪
♪ مهما حدث
♪You share my dreams♪
♪ أنت تشاركني أحلامي ♪
♪You share my sorrow♪
♪ أنت تشاركني حزني ♪
♪It reminds me♪
إنه يذكرني ♪
♪Not to fall when I'm tired♪
♪ لا أسقط وأنا متعب ♪
♪Behind me♪
♪ ورائي ♪
♪There's a friend♪
♪ هناك صديق
♪That's♪
♪ هذا ♪
♪The cape on my shoulders♪
♪ الرداء على كتفي ♪
♪You know everything about me♪
♪ أنت تعرف كل شيء عني ♪
♪Never back down♪
لا تتراجع أبدًا
♪In the sky♪
في السماء ♪
♪We look at the shining stars♪
♪ ننظر إلى النجوم الساطعة
♪The fluttering cape♪
♪ الحرملة المرفرفة ♪